Peace in the war
Benevolence and cruelty
I tread my own path in this divided land
The fields are busy
A big harvest requires many hands
That the other
And merchant looks uneasy
I will not tolerate this to suspect
Well you are a friendly beast
Are you not
Some i said this way
I beg you hurry
Sir
Please
Right behind you
Little one
Oh baba
I brought someone in my room
I wonder where you wait
A samurai
One that does not hail from these ants
I am a stranger
Yes
But you have nothing to fear from me
I have enough to fear from the men of kushyama
They abuse their power
Taxing us again and again
Leaving us only scraps
I bet they are in the market now
Along the main road
A stranger might make good merit
Leading a village of a threat
Like these men
Is that so then i shall see it done for this life
If not the next
What is happening here
This isn't your fight
Samurai
I told you keep walking
Make your peace
You won't need to kill me
Thank you
There's another of the world for the castle of corrupt samurai would
Greed cannot rule this village
Not while i have breath in my lungs
And a blade in my head
I'll wash away his failure with your blood
You have to spill it first
Who do you think you are for the people
I was going to handle this
Too slow
What did you find
This samurai has been stealing from the villagers
He has been staffing the people here for some time
So now we know who he worked for
We should go not before we send our allies to look for him
He'll be difficult to find
Who will take the lead
We can sneak in or just through the front gate
It's almost dark
No one will see me coming
They will not stand a chance
But be careful in there
Don't worry
I won't be alone
It'll be me in the shadows
The shadows to serve the light
I'll go straight for the dino when fighting a snake
Why wrestle the body when you can slice off the head
You're my now snake
Who did that
Lord
How i cannot seem to stay to war
A grave
Huh
He's coming
I need to hide
Fujioka dies in the street at the hands of some stranger
You serve me scalding tea
Besides ruining its delicate flavour
I nearly lose my tongue of this
Frioka must have been the samurai yasi took out good riddance
Take your time
A daimyo
Like that
Deserves a slower death than the one i'm about to give him
I've shed all the blood
I need time to go
To being allies